<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<anime>
  <entry>
    <id>71</id>
    <title>Full Metal Panic!</title>
    <english>Full Metal Panic!</english>
    <synonyms>FMP</synonyms>
    <episodes>24</episodes>
    <score>8.09</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2002-01-08</start_date>
    <end_date>2002-06-18</end_date>
    <synopsis>
      Sousuke Sagara, a seventeen year old military specialist working for the secret organization MITHRIL, has been assigned to protect the latest &amp;quot;Whispered&amp;quot; candidate Kaname Chidori. To complete this task Sousuke will have to deal with enemies from his past as well as the occasional panty thief. Unfortunately for Sousuke, the toughest part of his mission isn&amp;#039;t only protecting Miss Chidori but also getting used to living an average High School students life, no easy task for someone raised on the battlefield.&lt;br /&gt;
      &lt;br /&gt;
      (Source: ANN)
    </synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/6/9549.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>72</id>
    <title>Full Metal Panic? Fumoffu</title>
    <english>Full Metal Panic? Fumoffu</english>
    <synonyms>Full Metal Panic Fumoffu</synonyms>
    <episodes>12</episodes>
    <score>8.53</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2003-08-26</start_date>
    <end_date>2003-10-18</end_date>
    <synopsis>
      It&amp;#039;s back-to-school mayhem with Kaname Chidori and her war-freak classmate Sousuke Sagara as they encounter more misadventures in and out of Jindai High School. But when Kaname gets into some serious trouble, Sousuke takes the guise of Bonta-kun - the gun-wielding, butt-kicking mascot. And while he struggles to continue living as a normal teenager, Sousuke also has to deal with protecting his superior officer Teletha Testarossa, who has decided to take a vacation from Mithril and spend a couple of weeks as his and Kaname&amp;#039;s classmate.&lt;br /&gt;
      &lt;br /&gt;
      (Source: ANN)
    </synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/13/21580.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>73</id>
    <title>Full Metal Panic! The Second Raid</title>
    <english>Full Metal Panic! The Second Raid</english>
    <synonyms>Full Metal Panic! TSR</synonyms>
    <episodes>13</episodes>
    <score>8.32</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2005-07-14</start_date>
    <end_date>2005-10-20</end_date>
    <synopsis>
      This series is set about two months after the events ocurred in the Tuatha de Danaan at the end of the original series. Mithril becomes aware of a secret organization that has technology able to counter the ECS (Electronic Cloaking System) mode. This organization, known as Amalgam, also has &amp;quot;Black Technology&amp;quot;, obtained from &amp;quot;Whispered&amp;quot; like Kaname Chidori, and like the other intelligency agencies, they intend to obtain more. However, when Sousuke&amp;#039;s mission to protect Chidori is terminated by Mithril, all seems to be in place for Amalgam&amp;#039;s plans... Like many of its fans know, it is based of the FMP novel &amp;quot;The End of Day by Day.&amp;quot;&lt;br /&gt;
      (Source: ANN)
    </synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/4/5710.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>121</id>
    <title>Fullmetal Alchemist</title>
    <english>Fullmetal Alchemist</english>
    <synonyms>Hagane no Renkinjutsushi; FMA; Full Metal Alchemist</synonyms>
    <episodes>51</episodes>
    <score>8.63</score>
    <type>TV</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2003-10-04</start_date>
    <end_date>2004-10-02</end_date>
    <synopsis>The rules of alchemy state that to gain something, one must lose something of equal value. Alchemy is the process of taking apart and reconstructing an object into a different entity, with the rules of alchemy to govern this procedure. However, there exists an object that can bring any alchemist above these rules, the object known as the Philosopher&amp;#039;s Stone. The young Edward Elric is a particularly talented alchemist who through an accident years back lost his younger brother Alphonse and one of his legs. Sacrificing one of his arms as well, he used alchemy to bind his brother&amp;#039;s soul to a suit of armor. This lead to the beginning of their journey to restore their bodies, in search for the legendary Philosopher&amp;#039;s Stone.</synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/2/17621.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>1015</id>
    <title>Full Metal Panic! The Second Raid OVA</title>
    <english>Full Metal Panic! The Second Raid OVA</english>
    <synonyms>Wari to Hima na Sentaichou no Ichinichi, The Commanding Officer's Rather Quiet Day</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>8.01</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2006-05-26</start_date>
    <end_date>2006-05-26</end_date>
    <synopsis>
      On her day off, Tessa wakes up in her commander chair. After regaining her composure, she notices that her favorite stuffed animal is missing and thus tries to remember what actually transpired the night before. To do so, she will spend time with all the main characters of the Danaan crew, and eventually recalls the events of the previous night.&lt;br /&gt;
      &lt;br /&gt;
      [Written by MAL Rewrite]
    </synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/3/23458.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>2601</id>
    <title>Heavy Metal L-Gaim III: Full Metal Soldier</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Heavy Metal L-Gaim OVA</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>0.00</score>
    <type>OVA</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>1987-03-28</start_date>
    <end_date>1987-03-28</end_date>
    <synopsis>
      No synopsis has been added for this series yet.&lt;br /&gt;
      &lt;br /&gt;
      &lt;!--link--&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://myanimelist.net/dbchanges.php?aid=2601&amp;amp;t=synopsis&quot;&gt;Click here&lt;/a&gt; to update this information.
    </synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/3/24615.jpg</image>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>6291</id>
    <title>Full Metal Panic! The Second Raid Episode 000</title>
    <english></english>
    <synonyms>Full Metal Panic! The Second Raid Pre-festival: Night of the Light Novel</synonyms>
    <episodes>1</episodes>
    <score>7.78</score>
    <type>Special</type>
    <status>Finished Airing</status>
    <start_date>2005-07-06</start_date>
    <end_date>2005-07-06</end_date>
    <synopsis>
      Sousuke, Kurz and Melissa are deployed to the Republic of Manistan in Central Asia to eradicate a growing civil war between rebels and the Manistani military. &lt;br /&gt;
      &lt;br /&gt;
      (Source: Wikipedia)
    </synopsis>
    <image>http://cdn.myanimelist.net/images/anime/2/14059.jpg</image>
  </entry>
</anime>
